flighthub.com 2018-12-29

# Privacy Policy

Just as our staff regard their privacy as paramount, your privacy is very important to us at Flighthub. With that in mind, we have established information handling practices for Flighthub that we believe are consistent with the highest standards and best practices of organisations doing business on the Internet, as well as complying with relevant legislation.

This privacy policy ('Policy') describes the practices that apply to our web site, including, specifically, the information we collect about you, when and how we collect that information and what may happen to that information.

Flighthub has prepared a detailed privacy policy because we believe you should know as much as possible about our practices so that you can make an informed decision about the extent of your use of our facilities.

**Simply stated:**

  * Flighthub will not collect personally identifiable information like your name, e-mail and mailing address and telephone number ('Personal Information') without your knowledge and permission; 
  * Flighthub will not disclose your Personal Information to third parties unless you have authorized us to do so, or required to do so by law; 
  * Flighthub will allow you to view, correct or remove your Personal Information and other information associated with your registration as a user of our site; and
  * Flighthub will take reasonable steps to protect the security of the Personal Information we collect from you.

**OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

**Perusing our web site content**

You can visit our site without revealing who you are or providing any Personal Information.

When you visit our site we do collect usage information, but it is anonymous and is not linked to you as an individual. We use this data to better understand things like how our site is navigated, how many visitors arrive at specific pages, the length and frequency of stays at our site, the variety of searches of our site's database, the types of browsers and computer operating systems used by our visitors and the Internet Protocol addresses from which our visitors connect to our site.

This information is regularly collected by Internet server software on most sites.

Flighthub uses this information to improve our site content and ease of use, for instance, providing easier access to popular web pages.

**Cookies and Pixel Tagging**

Flighthub, or a third-party advertiser we link to, may place a 'cookie' or 'pixel tag' on your personal computer when you visit the site or visit a site on which we advertise.

These devices are small computer files that our computer sends to your computer and that your computer sends back to us each time you make a request from our site.

These devices are used to collect data to help us personalize and improve your experiences on web sites. The data on your use of a web site may be linked to the Personal Information you have chosen to share with us when you register.

Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies.

However, you can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or prompt you before accepting a cookie from the sites you visit.

If you decide not to accept our cookies, your ability to use some features on some web site may be impaired.

You can learn more about the use of cookies, pixel tags and other devices, the information gathering practices of our network-advertising partners, and about opting out, by visiting http://networkadvertising.org.

**Third-party Advertisers**

Internet marketing companies advertise on the Internet, and Flighthub, may, at some future date, have third-party advertisers on this site. Third-party advertisers may use cookies and pixel tags to gather information about the ads you have seen and the types of things that you appear interested in.

Flighthub does not share any Personal Information about you with these advertisers unless you give us specific permission to do so, separate from any permission you provide during a registration process.

These advertisers may use combined information about your visits to our site and other sites in order to provide advertisements about related goods and services that you may be interested in. This privacy policy does not cover the policies or practices of these third-party advertisers.

We offer personalized shopping experiences and advertising through Intent Media, which uses online identifiers to identify visitors. To view Intent Media’s privacy policy, click [here](http://intentmedia.com/privacy-policy/). To opt out, click [here](http://www.intentmedia.com/opt-out).

**Personal Information**

If you decide to register with us, we will collect Personal Information about you that you voluntarily share with us. We collect Personal Information that is necessary for us to provide you with the services offered on our site. As mentioned, this Personal Information includes things like your name, e-mail and mailing address and telephone number.

**Traveller Profile**

Flighthub combines your Personal Information and other information you voluntarily share with us in what we call your 'Traveller Profile'.

We also add the data about how you use our web site to your Traveler Profile. We may also collect information about you from outside sources and add it to your Traveler Profile, such as e-tickets or itineraries from airline companies.

We collect and use all of the information in your Traveller Profile to improve the quality of our service to you and your experience with us.

By way of example, we may use the combination of information in your Traveller Profile to (a) personalize the service we provide to you, (b) communicate with you about changes to your travel plans, service updates and new features or outages on our site, and (c) allocate the resources of our systems so that your experience with our site is as efficient as possible.

**Opt-out**

As part of the registration process, we give you the choice to either receive or opt-out from receiving advertisements, updates and promotions via e-mail.

If you choose to receive the above items we hope you will find them interesting and informative. In fact, we will use the information you tell us about your travel preferences and experiences to share customized advertisements, updates and promotions with you that include our recommendations to you about travel specials.

You should let us know if you do not want us to use your e-mail addresses to deliver to you: (1) our deals updates highlighting flight specials, promotions, and other travel opportunities available on our web site and/or sponsored by our travel service providers and advertisers; and/or (2) our monthly newsletter, when it becomes available, highlighting flight specials, promotions, contests, sweepstakes and other travel opportunities available on our site and/or sponsored by our travel service providers.

We use different methods, including an e-mail delivery and marketing company, to send the e-mails that you have agreed to receive.

Pixel tags and cookies may be used in those e-mail messages and at our website to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising and to study how visitors use our site.

Should you no longer wish to receive our promotions, you may use the unsubscribe link included in any email message that we send you. If you are a registered member, you can also modify your choice at any time on the [Account Manager](https://www.flighthub.com/my-account) page.

**On-line Surveys and Contests**

We value your comments and opinions. From time to time, we will invite you, as a registered user of our site, to participate in online surveys, but the choice will be yours.

Each time you purchase, book or reserve travel services or accommodations through our site your Travel Consultant may ask for your feedback on your experience.

Your participation in these surveys is on an anonymous basis, unless we tell you up-front otherwise.

We may offer you the chance to win a variety of travel related prizes by sponsoring contests. You choose to participate in these contests or not. If you choose to participate in these contests, you will share certain of your Personal Information with us, like your full name, e-mail address and mailing address.

Participation in these contests may include participation in an on-line survey. We will only use your Personal Information to notify you if you win a contest.

**Payment Information and Travel History**

If you register with us, you will be able to book, reserve or purchase travel services or accommodations through our site.

To do so, you must provide payment information to us - for example, your credit card specifics like card number, expiration date, cardholder name and billing address.

We will add this payment information to your Traveller Profile.

We will keep a history of all your reservations, bookings and purchases of travel services and accommodations through our site in your Traveller Profile, unless you choose to edit your Traveller Profile as described below in this policy (Changing and Removing Personal Information and Other Information).

**Itinerary changes & Travel Alerts**

If you book, reserve or purchase travel services through our site, you will have the option to receive and/or have others receive last minute updates about your travel arrangements, such as changes in gate assignment or delays in departure or arrival time.

'These 'Travel Itinerary & Travel Alerts' can be received by you or others of your choosing via telephone, cell phone, e-mail, pager or other wireless device.

If you decide to direct a Travel Itinerary & Travel Alert to someone other than yourself, we will collect Personal Information about that other person that is necessary to send the requested Travel Itinerary & Travel Alert (i.e., that person's name and phone number or e-mail address).

You will need to make sure that each of the other recipients of a Travel Itinerary & Travel Alert agrees, in advance, that you can disclose their Personal Information to us for this purpose.

**Sharing of Personal Information**

Generally, we only disclose your Personal Information to those travel providers that you decide to make arrangements with through our site.

For example, when you purchase an airline ticket or reserve a rental car or hotel room, we will provide the airline, car rental agency or hotel, as the case may be, with the Personal Information needed to process your transaction.

We use our reasonable efforts to ensure that these travel providers will also protect your Personal Information.

We contract other companies to perform various functions necessary to operate our business - for example, to deliver tickets, ship items and process credit cards. We will share with these other companies only that Personal Information they require to fulfill your orders. These companies agree that they will not use or disclose that Personal Information for any other purpose.

Other than as explained in this policy, we will not disclose any Personal Information we collect from you to others without your permission, except in certain limited circumstances: (a) to protect the security of our web site and our rights under our Terms and Conditions of Use; (b) to protect ourselves against liability; (c) in response to legal process, (d) if we believe in good faith that the law requires it; or (e) in connection with a sale of our business or company; (f) as required by governmental security regulations.

We shall always advise you when such unusual disclosures are made.

It should be remembered that should you choose to request certain services such as religious or special diet meals certain religious or health information may be deduced by the Travel Provider and your permission is automatically granted to forward such information when you make such special requests.

Furthermore, any Travellers to/from the U.S. may have their data captured by the U.S. Homeland Security Agency, which can store it for up to 50 years. This information can be shared with other U.S. Government Agencies.

**Corporate Travel**

If you, or someone acting on your behalf, purchase(s) travel services or accommodations through our site and (a) you, or someone acting on your behalf, tell(s) us that your purchase is for corporate travel purposes either by indicating in the booking path that the purchase is for corporate travel or indicating that the credit card being used is a corporate credit card and (b) we have entered into an agreement with your corporation to provide data on the purchase of travel services or accommodations by the corporation's personnel, we will provide your corporation with the Personal Information necessary for the corporation to track your corporate travel purchased on our site.

**Other Travellers**

If you decide to book, reserve or purchase travel services or accommodations for other Travellers using your Traveller Profile, we will collect certain Personal Information about these other Travellers.

You will need to make sure that each of these other travellers agrees, in advance, that you can disclose their Personal Information to us. We will retain these other travellers' Personal Information in your Traveller Profile.

**Links to Other Sites**

Our site provides links to other sites. When you click on one of these links, you are leaving our site and entering another site that we do not control and for which we cannot be responsible.

You should carefully review the privacy statements or policies on any other site that you visit because those privacy statements or policies will apply to your visit to that site and may be very different from our policy.

In some cases, for example the purchase of travel insurance, our site will link you directly to our partner's site where you may be asked to provide Personal Information. This privacy policy will not cover the use of your Personal Information by these other companies.

We encourage you to read each other company's privacy policy before signing up for any of its products or services.

**Changing/Removing Personal Information or Other Information**

We are committed to giving you control over your Personal Information. You can change your password and any of the Personal Information or Other Information in your Traveller Profile, by contacting your Travel Consultant.

If at any time you want to view the Personal Information or Other Information in your Traveller Profile, your Personal Information changes, you want to change the preferences associated with your account, or would like us to remove some or all of the Personal Information or Other Information stored in your Traveller Profile, you can correct, update, or remove the information and preferences you have shared with us by contacting your Travel Consultant.

If you request that we remove all of the Personal Information and Other Information stored in your Traveler Profile, then we will promptly do so. In this case you will not be able to use our services available unless you re-register.

Similarly, we will remove all of your travel records within seven (7) months after receiving a request to do so.

This seven (7) month period is necessary to ensure that travel arrangements made through our site are properly accounted for as well as allowing for the redundancy of our CD-ROM data back-up system.

We may not be able to honour your request to remove your Personal Information or travel records if we are legally obligated to retain that information or those records.

You will not have the ability to view, change or remove session data or information that we have gathered from Third Parties from your Traveller Profile - unless you are able to make such arrangements with them.

Some records, such as taxation or other financial records have to be retained for up to 7 years, and we are obliged by law to comply.

**Notification of Changes**

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we decide to change this policy in a material way (for example, a change regarding disclosure of Personal Information), we will post notice of the change on our site or notify you via e-mail at the address you have provided to us or pop-up screen at least thirty (30) days before putting the change into effect.

If we decide to change our policy in a less significant way, we will simply post notice of the change on our site at least thirty (30) days before putting the change into effect.

If any proposed change is unacceptable to you, you may, as discussed in the section above (Changing and Removing Personal and Other Information), request that we remove your Personal Information from our records.

**Combined Non-Personal Information**

We may also combine anonymous information supplied by you and other users during registration on our site with information about your use and others' use of our site.

We will use this combined information to describe our user base, without reference to any specific individual, to potential partners, investors and advertisers.

We will not share your Personal Information with any other users of our site, but we may use information we collect about your travel preferences and experiences to make recommendations to other users of our site.

By way of example, if we know that you and other users of our site who have traveled to a particular destination had positive experiences at a hotel in that destination, we might recommend that hotel to others who will be traveling to that destination.

We may also share aggregated statistical information about users of our site and our service and product offerings with others, including our vendors and partners.

We will not link this statistical information to any Personal Information that can identify you as an individual.

**How We Protect Your Information**

We are committed to safeguarding your information. For that reason we employ security technology professionals and utilise a full range of the best security technology available.

Specifically, your information is secured from unauthorised access from the Internet through leading firewall technology, Virtual Private Networks and alarm systems.

We, or our associates, also protect the connection between your computer and our server from eavesdropping through industry-standard encryption technology known as Secure Socket Layer (SSL).

Depending on your browser, this SSL will have encryption keys of up to 128 bits. To ensure that we fulfill our commitment to safeguard your information, we continually assess new technology for protecting your information to make sure that our information handling practices are in accordance with the highest industry standards and best practices on the Internet at all times.

**Children and Minors**

Children and Minors (individuals under 18 years of age) - are not eligible to register for or use the services available on our site.

Flighthub staff are parents and Flighthub believes that parents should play a central role in their child's on-line activities and should monitor those activities to ensure that sites visited by their child, or minor, are respecting their child's privacy.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this policy or our information handling practices, you may contact us via e-mail at [support@Flighthub.com](mailto:support@Flighthub.com) . We will attempt to respond to your questions or concerns within five (5) business days after we receive them.

**Flighthub Inc.**  
250 Water Street, Suite 205B, Summerside, P.E.I. C1N 1B6
